internationalcheckout.com 2011-11-23

# :: International Checkout :: Delivering products from America to your doorstep, worldwide ::

Privacy Policy  
We value your trust and respect your privacy and are committed to protecting both. We believe that you have the right to know how we collect your personal information and how we use it. This privacy statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: www.internationalcheckout.com. By using this web site you accept and agree to be bound by the terms of this privacy statement. If you do not agree with this privacy statement please do not use this web site. If you have any questions about this policy you can click here, or contact us by phone at 001 3.... This privacy statement, provides the following information: What information we collect from you. How we use the information we collect. Do we share your information ? What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your information. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information we collect about you.

[top]

Information Collection & Use  
Registration In order to place an order on this web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give us contact information (such as name, country and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on this web site. We may also use this information to inform you about new features, new services and special offers. If you do not want us to use your information to contact you about services or offers that may be of interest to you, you can opt out by following the instructions below under "Choice/Opt-out." Orders We will also use information gathered on this web site to process your orders. If you purchase a product through us, certain personally identifiable information will be requested from you on your order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, telephone number and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). The information you provide us will be used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order this information will also be used to contact you.

[top]

Registration  
In order to place an order on this web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give us contact information (such as name, country and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on this web site. We may also use this information to inform you about new features, new services and special offers. If you do not want us to use your information to contact you about services or offers that may be of interest to you, you can opt out by following the instructions below under "Choice/Opt-out."

[top]

Orders  
We will also use information gathered on this web site to process your orders. If you purchase a product through us, certain personally identifiable information will be requested from you on your order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, telephone number and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). The information you provide us will be used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order this information will also be used to contact you.

[top]

Sharing Information With Other Companies or People  
We do not sell, rent, trade, or lease your personal information for marketing purposes, or for any other purposes, other than as specifically identified in this privacy statement. We share your first and last name with Merchant for "transactional purposes." Apart from our own marketing purposes, we will allow Merchant access to and use of your personally identifiable information to inform you about Merchant's products, services and special offers. If you do not want us to use your personally identifiable information for marketing purposes, or if you do not want us to share your information with Merchant for Merchant's marketing purposes, you can opt-out by following the instructions under "Choice/Opt-out" below. Other than as described herein, your personally identifiable information may be disclosed only in good faith when we are required to do so by law, or when disclosure is reasonably necessary for us to comply with legal process, respond to any claims, or to protect our rights, property or personal safety, our customers or the public.

[top]

Information Collection & Use  
Registration In order to place an order on this web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give us contact information (such as name, country and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on this web site. We may also use this information to inform you about new features, new services and special offers. If you do not want us to use your information to contact you about services or offers that may be of interest to you, you can opt out by following the instructions below under "Choice/Opt-out." Orders We will also use information gathered on this web site to process your orders. If you purchase a product through us, certain personally identifiable information will be requested from you on your order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, telephone number and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). The information you provide us will be used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order this information will also be used to contact you.

[top]

Note for European Customers  
The information you provide to us will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purpose of processing by us, our affiliates and agents. By submitting your information, you agree to that international transfer. We meet the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

[top]

Logged Files and Cookies  
This web site logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration and payment fraud control purposes. These logs are analyzed to manage payment fraud and improve the value of the materials available on the web site. User's sessions are tracked, but the user remains anonymous. We link IP addresses to personally identifiable information to process your payments. This web site also uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We link the information stored in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on this web site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate this web site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. We use cookies to identify you during your session, to make services easier to use and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers or passwords. Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to browse this web site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to prevent that. The information you provide to us will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purpose of processing by us, our affiliates and agents. By submitting your information, you agree to that international transfer. We meet the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

[top]

Links To Other Web Sites  
International Checkout may offer links to other independent third party web sites. Please note that when you enter those web sites using our links, International Checkout bears no liability for the contents thereof.

[top]

Security  
Protecting your privacy and your personally identifiable information is a top priority. We take commercially reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedurals safeguards in order to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personally identifiable information. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on order forms, this information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Once your information is received by this web site it is stored behind a firewall. We ensure that all of our employees are aware of these privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs. Despite all of these precautions, by using this web site, you acknowledge that the Internet is inherently insecure and that there is always a risk that your personally identifiable information could be intercepted or otherwise accessed and improperly used.

[top]

Accessing and Correcting Your Information  
Accessing and Correcting Your Information If at any time you decide that you do not want either us or Merchant to use any of the personally identifiable information collected on this site, or if you believe that this information is incorrect, you should click here. Alternatively, you may write to the following address: International CHeckout, Inc. 11973 Montana Ave, Suite 1, Los Angeles California 90049. Upon receipt of any notification from you regarding the preceding sentence we will promptly stop using your personally identifiable information, or, if it is the case, promptly correct any incorrect information, and we will require Merchant to do the same. We strongly encourage you to request a confirming e-mail in the event you send your request by e-mail, or if you contact us by mail you should do so via certified mail, return receipt requested. In most cases, you can expect a response to your request within 14 business days.

[top]

Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy  
We reserve the right to modify, add or remove portions of this privacy statement at any time. The latest version of this privacy statement is contained on this web site and indicates the date that it went into affect. You are encouraged to review this privacy statement whenever you use this web site to make sure you always understand how your information is used. If changes are made to this privacy statement, those changes will be posted on this web site. If at any point we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner that is materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, you will be notified by email. If Merchant decides to use your personally identifiable information in a materially different manner we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of such change. You will always have a choice as to whether or not your information is used by us in a materially different manner.

[top]
